{"message": "Successfully uploaded", "questions": [{"explanation": "lifted is Verb (past tense)", "question": "Select appropiate Verb (past tense) from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he _____________ his paw and let him go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["tied", "was", "lifted", "went"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: was", "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (past tense).", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["and", "paw", "let", "was"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: paw", "question": "In the following sentence identify Singular or mass Noun.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["that", "paw", "by", "help"]}, {"explanation": "by is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled _____________ the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["in", "after", "of", "by"]}, {"explanation": "mouse is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the _____________ being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["mouse", "tree", "idea", "search"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: few", "question": "In the following sentence identify Adjective.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["tied", "tree", "captured", "few"]}, {"explanation": "of is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search _____________ a wagon , to take him to the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["by", "of", "that", "after"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: tied", "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (past tense).", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["tied", "to", "and", "a"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: tickled", "question": "In the following sentence identify Adjective.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["tickled", "of", "that", "to"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: lion", "question": "In the following sentence identify Singular or mass Noun.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["to", "lion", "able", "lifted"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: hunters", "question": "In the following sentence identify Pural Noun.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["hunters", "a", "a", "lion"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: in", "question": "In the following sentence identify Preposition or subordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["they", "the", "take", "in"]}, {"explanation": "take is Verb (base form)", "question": "Select appropiate Verb (base form) from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to _____________ him to the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["help", "go", "let", "take"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: zoo", "question": "In the following sentence identify Singular or mass Noun.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["zoo", "a", "him", "to"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: idea", "question": "In the following sentence identify Singular or mass Noun.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["his", "go", "idea", "him"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: that", "question": "In the following sentence identify Preposition or subordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["to", "zoo", "that", "they"]}, {"explanation": "search is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "After that they went in _____________ of a wagon , to take him to the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["zoo", "search", "idea", "mouse"]}, {"explanation": "tied is Verb (past tense)", "question": "Select appropiate Verb (past tense) from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and _____________ him to a tree .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["went", "lifted", "was", "tied"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: tree", "question": "In the following sentence identify Singular or mass Noun.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["hunters", "tree", "later", "captured"]}, {"explanation": "lion is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The _____________ was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["lion", "mouse", "paw", "search"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: of", "question": "In the following sentence identify Preposition or subordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["of", "went", "wagon", "take"]}, {"explanation": "that is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "After _____________ they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["that", "after", "by", "in"]}, {"explanation": "lion is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the _____________ , and tied him to a tree .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["search", "paw", "mouse", "lion"]}], "success": 1}